http://www.bedwettingstore.com/pages/privacy-policy

Bedwetting Alarms
Treatment Kits
Why choose a treatment kit? Kits comes with everything you need to get started. Alarm of your choosing, underpads for quick changes, and a book to guide you. Plus, save over $28 over buying items individually.
Bedwetting Alarms
Treatment Kits
Why choose a treatment kit? Kits comes with everything you need to get started. Alarm of your choosing, underpads for quick changes, and a book to guide you. Plus, save over $28 over buying items individually.
Daytime Washable Briefs
Timed Voiding Watches
Is your child struggling during the day? Try setting a vibrating watch to remind them to use the restroom and use washable briefs for daytime accidents.
Daytime Washable Briefs
Timed Voiding Watches
Is your child struggling during the day? Try setting a vibrating watch to remind them to use the restroom and use washable briefs for daytime accidents.
Bedding
Stain Removers
Protect your bed with a wide variety of mattress covers or underpads. Clean your bed with our tried and tested stain removers.
Bedding
Stain Removers
Protect your bed with a wide variety of mattress covers or underpads. Clean your bed with our tried and tested stain removers.
Disposable Underwear
Disposable Underpads
Products for both adults and children, we carry disposable diapers and briefs plus underpads to protect your furniture and beds.
Disposable Underwear
Disposable Underpads
Products for both adults and children, we carry disposable diapers and briefs plus underpads to protect your furniture and beds.
Alarm Accessories
Books
Need something extra for your alarm?  Perhaps you want a book to help motivate your child or help to guide you, the parent, on how to help your child achieve dryness.
Alarm Accessories
Books
Need something extra for your alarm?  Perhaps you want a book to help motivate your child or help to guide you, the parent, on how to help your child achieve dryness.
Privacy and Security
Security Standards
The Bedwetting Store is aware of the potential threat of online identity and information theft. We make every effort possible to ensure your information is confidential and secure. We have implemented the services of McAfee SECURE and SSL Certificates. For in depth information please visit the individual websites.
Information Collection and Use
The Bedwetting Store is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The Bedwetting Store collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
Reviews, Comments and Questions
Users are welcome and encouraged to post reviews and comments on products, as well as ask questions. These comments may or may not be available for public viewing. Under no circumstance should a review, comment or question contain any inflammatory, illegal, threatening, obscene, private or other injurious material. No review, comment or question should be written by any person impersonating another. The Bedwetting Store and its affiliates are entitled to nonexclusive rights to use, modify or otherwise adjust, publish, translate, reproduce, and/or distribute any review, comment or question without the user consent and without compensation of any form. The Bedwetting Store has no obligation to edit or remove any content posted by a user or third party. The Bedwetting Store assumes no liability or responsibility for any content posted by you or any third party.
Orders
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address and phone numbers) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside order and credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies may retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information in accordance with the policies that govern their order processing services.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we at the Bedwetting Store are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.
Special Offers
Established customers may occasionally receive information on products, services, or services. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
If a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done by emailing our Customer Support.
Choice/Opt-out
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having information or newsletters emailed to them. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the unsubscribing instructions, replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or emailing us at service@bedwettingstore.com
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Subscribe Sign up to get the latest on sales, new releases and more …
x
x
